Guide to the Justice Stephen G. Crane Papers on the Bernhard Goetz Trial and Other Cases 1981–2000 MS 3152
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. People v. Goetz trial artifacts, 1987
  - Autographed jury box remnant, [1987 May 1] (Object Artifact)
    Also signing: Justice Stephen G. Crane; Law Secretary, Leon Schechter; Court Clerk Robert Hamkalo; Assistant District Attorney Gregory Waples; Defense Team, Barry Slotnick; Mark M. Baker; Frank King; Gillian Coulter; and Bernhard Goetz; Court Officers Jim Lawler; Dan Dolger; Clifton Murphy; Stephen Cazilas; and Artie Coardes; and Court Reporters Stephen Cohen; Joel Machlis; Nina Koss; and Hilda J. Wall.
    The reverse side of the board shows the finish that was visible on the exterior of the jury box.
  - Autographed jury admonition / oath, 1987 May 28 (Offsite-box 1)
    A rolled scroll of ten attached sheets of continuous form, dot matrix printer paper (measuring approximately 108 inches long by 15 inches high), with the following message and inscription (in capital letters):
    WE, THE JURORS, AGREE: TO KEEP AN OPEN MIND ON EVERY ISSUE INVOLVING THIS CASE; NOT TO DISCUSS ANY ELEMENT OF THIS CASE AMONG OURSELVES OR WITH ANYONE ELSE; NOT TO READ, WATCH OR LISTEN ABOUT THIS CASE AS IT IS REPORTED BY THE MEDIA; TO PROMPTLY REPORT TO THE COURT ANY ATTEMPT BY ANYONE TO IMPROPERLY INFLUENCE ANY MEMBER OF THIS JURY. -- JAMES, ERNIECE, CATHERINE, WIRTH, MARK, JAMES II, LYN, DIANA, ROBERT, FRANCISCO, MICHAEL, RALPH, JON, DELPHINE, LOU, AUGIE.
    TO JUSTICE STEPHEN G. CRANE WITH RESPECT AND ADMIRATION MAY 28, 1987
    Signed next to their printed names by jurors James Hurley, Erniece Dix, Catherine Brody, D. Wirth Jackson, Mark Lesly, James Mosely, Carolyn Perlmuth, Diana Serpe, Robert Leach, Francisco Figueroa, Michael Axelrod, Ralph Schriempf, and alternates Jon Patten, Delphine McFadden, Lou Vereen, and Augustine Ayala.